Guide to the Grace Cavalieri papers, 1945-2022 MS2007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Writings, Production, and Publicity, 1956-2019; Series 5
  - One Act Plays Volume one [4/4], undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Plays include: "Hush, No One Is Listening", "We Regret to Inform You That The Destiny Of Future Generations Is Uncertain Because of a General Inability On The Part Of All Night Watchmen", "What Shall We Do Yesterday?"
  - One Act Plays Volume two [1/3], undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Plays include: "What A Place Not To Have A Bridge", "Cake In The Land of Elbows", "The Wide Game", "Box of Invisible". This folder also includes a CD-ROM
  - One Act Plays Volume two [2/3], undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Plays include: "Mary Wollstonecraft", "In The Land of Elbows", "At Last Alone Together", "Harvest Kitchen", "Getting Ready", "The Rehearsal".
  - One Act Plays Volume two [3/3], undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Plays include: "Stripping", "Jennie and the Jujuman"
  - The Sticker Tree by Grace Cavalieri, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven by Grace Cavalieri, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Quiliting the Sun by Grace Cavalieri, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Hyena in Petticoats by Grace Cavalieri, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars - drafts [1/6], 03/10/1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars - drafts [2/6], 05/18/1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars - drafts [3/6], 05/22/1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars - drafts [4/6], 08/02/1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars - drafts [5/6], undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Amidst the Seven Stars - drafts [6/6], undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Ann Darr: Tribute, undated (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Anna Nicole: Images and Others, undated (Box 88, Folder 27)
    Anna Nicole Images and Others
    Handwritten notes about Anna Nicole poems and related topics
  - "Anna Nicole: Poems" Review, 12/2008 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    Review
    Review of "Anna NIcole: Poems" in the Baltimore City Paper.
  - Anne Caston: Article in the Northern Light, undated (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Anything for Wisement, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Apropos Mot, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Awards and certificates, 1985-2007 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Backyard Fun, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Best American Poetry, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Bibliography, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Biographical information and resumes, 1977-1997 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Birds That Call Before the Rain, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Bliss, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Body Fluids, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Callaloo vol.24 no.4, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - Cavalieri Reading event notice, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Cavalieri's Student Article, 2008 (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Clippings, 1976-2007 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Citation from Montgomery County, 2017; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Comments and Publications, 2015 March; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - A compendium of celebrants The Tenth Anniversary of Dolores Kendrick DC Poet Laureate, 11/22/2009; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Cora Poems, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Cuffed Frays, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Dates, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Death of a Child by Beating or Not, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Devy Bendit, 1985-1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Emily Clark Balch Prize Contest, 1956-2006 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Epithalamions, 2006-2007 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Essays, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Events and Readings, 1982-2005 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Events and Reviews, 1950-2011; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Evening of Irish Poetry: Brochure, 02/2008 (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - "Fear", undated (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Fly Up, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Flyer for Reading of "Anna Nicole: Poems", undated (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Folger Shakespeare Brochures, undated (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Fragments and ideas, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Getting ready, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Heads, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - HoCoPoLitSo, 10/2007 (Box 88, Folder 38)
    HoCoPoLitSo
    Howard County Poetry and Literature Society Annual Report. Article featuring Cavalieiri.
  - Howard Commuity College Brochure, 05/2008 (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - "How the Hand Behaves" Review, undated (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - Humanities Council of Washington Brochure, 1996-1997 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Humanities Council
    Cavalieri humorist of the year
  - Hush No One is Listening, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Hyena in Petticoats, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Interviews, 1992-2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Interviews and reviews by Grace Cavalieri, 2009; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to Cavalieri Poetry Reading, 10/2007 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Invitation to Georgetown University, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Iowa Sky A Memoir by Donald Gibson, 2013; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    This book was edited by Grace
  - Ivanhoe, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Jennie and the Jujuman, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Journal articles, 1999-2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Jumping to Conclusions, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - "The Keeper of the Station" play by Grace Cavalieri, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Dolores T. Kendrick and Eva Brann, 2017; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - The Late and Early Blooming Branch, 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Lecture: The Uses of Broadcasting, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Little Magazines, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - A Little Mysterious Bleeding, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Maryland Poet Laureate, 2019; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Memoir, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Michael Glaser DVD, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Michael Lally Big Deal # 4, 1976; series 5 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Millie's Sunshine Tiki Villas, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Miporadio, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Missy's Review: "Anna Nicole: Poems", 09/2008 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Mrs. Powers and Miss Smith- drafts [1/6], 1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Mrs. Powers and Miss Smith- drafts [2/6], undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Mrs. Powers and Miss Smith- drafts [3/6], 1994-2000 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Mrs. Powers and Miss Smith- drafts [4/6], undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Powers and Miss Smith- drafts [5/6], undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Powers and Miss Smith- drafts [6/6], undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Arts A Woman Speaks poetry reading, 03/31/2010; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - New plays, 2009; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    Benji's Quilt and Anna Nicole
  - Nora, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Notebooks [1/7], 1970 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks [2/7], 1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Notebooks [3/7], 1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Notebooks [4/7], 2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Notebooks [5/7], 2000 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks [6/7], 2001-2005 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks [7/7], 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Old Favorites, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Old Woman in the Bed, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Other People's Arms, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - PEN Member Review of "Water on the Sun" by Cavalieri, 10/2007 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Permission forms, 1992-2006 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven, 1998-2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Includes photographs
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven correspondence, 1988-2004 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven draft [1/4], 1998 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven draft [2/4], 1999 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven draft [3/4], 1999 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Pinecrest Rest Haven draft [4/4], 1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Poems and fragments, 1967-2005 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Poems new and selected, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Poetry Events, 2012; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Poetry--Italian translations, 1999-2003 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Poetry-- Spanish translations, 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Poetry, uncollected, 1968-2007 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Poetry Magazine Radio Documentary [1/2], 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Poetry Magazine Radio Documentary [2/2], 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - The Poet's Cookbook Proposal, 2009 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Poet Laureate article, 01/2009 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Poets at Work, 05/2009 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    Poets at Work
    Article in "Bay Weekly"
  - Points In Space, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Points on the Meridian, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - PR [Public Relations], Undated; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - PR [Public Relations], 2015 October 15-17; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 2011; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Publications, 2012; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 2012; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Publications, 2012; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Publications, 2015; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Publications and press releases, 1987-2009; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Publications and Productions, 1998-2011; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Publications and productions, 2010; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Publications and Production, 2012; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Productions and Reviews, 2010-2011; Series 5 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Publications and PR [Public Relations][1/2], 2015; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Publications and PR [Public Relations][2/2], 2015 May 6; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1997-2016; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, 2011-2016; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 2016; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1967, 2017-2019; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Public relations, Reviews, Awards, Activities, Presentations, 1985-2013; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Public relations, Reviews, Publications, 2013 Spring; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Published works, 2001-2009; Series 5 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Quilting the Sun - correspondence, 10/03/1990 --01/04/2007 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [1/16], 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [2/16], 2000 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [3/16], 2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [4/16], 2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [5/16], 2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [6/16], 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [7/16], 11/07/2001 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [8/16], 2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [9/16], 2000-2002 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [10/16], undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [11/16], undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [12/16], undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [13/16], undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [14/16], undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [15/16], undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Quilting the Sun - drafts [16/16], undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Quilting the Sun- DVD, undated (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Quilting the Sun - notebooks [1/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Quilting the Sun - notebooks [2/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Quilting the Sun - notebooks [3/3], undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Quilting the Sun - performances [1/2], 2001-2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Quilting the Sun - performances [2/2], 2007 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Quilting the Sun - process, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Quilting the Sun - proposals and preliminary treatment, 1990-1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Quilting the Sun - reading script, 10/09/2002 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Quilting the Sun - research and notes, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Quilting the Sun- speech, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Quilting the Sun - premiere history, 1990-2010; series 5 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Reviews [1/2], 1982-2007 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Reviews [2/2], 1982-2007 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Reviews, Interviews, Press Releases, Circa 2011; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Reviews, Interviews, Press Releases, October 2014-January 2015; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Review of "Anna Nicole: Poems", undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Review of Shakespeare's "Twelfth Night", undated (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Richard Blanco Presidential Inauguration Poet 2013, Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Includes emails between Grace and Blanco, a copy of the poem "One Today" by Blando for the inauguation and a pamphlet from an event featuring Blanco
  - "Sally Dies" tribute, 06/2008 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Seven Colors for Victoria Blue, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Sotto Voce Poetry Festival brochures, 09/2008 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Split This Rock Poetry Festival, 03/2008 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Sticker Tree (Best of Friends), 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Best of Friends aka The Sticker Tree, 1974, 1987; Series 5 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Stripping, 1989-1996 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Subject to Change [1/3], 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Subject to Change [2/3], 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Subject to Change [3/3], 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Swan Research, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Theater brochures, undated (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Trenton, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Washington DC history, 1978 May; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    This folder includes a page from The Washingtonian magazine. This page is titled Poetry and includes three poems: "To My Dentist" by Jean Nordhaus; "Jesus" by E. Ethelbert Miller; "Dry Fly Fishing in Washington, D.C." by Chas. Centerfit Hart.
  - Washington Post Book World, Anna Nicole: Poems, undated (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Washington Post Book World "Spotlight on Poetry", 04/2008 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Water on the Sun, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Water on the Sun, undated (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - We Regret to Inform You, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Welcome to Washington videoscript, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - What Happened, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - What I Would Do For Love, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - What Shall We Do Yesterday, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - WPFW Newspaper, 03/1978 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - WPFW Newspaper, 03/1982-04/1983 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - WPFW Newspaper, 05/1983 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - WPFW Newspaper, 09/1983 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - WPFW Poetry Anthology, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - WPFW Remembers brochure, undated (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Writer's Carousel: Moderated by Grace Cavalieri, undated (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - You and Me, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - You and Me, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Quilting the Sun, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Oversize item
  - Awards and certificates, 2005-2007 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Swan Research, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Poetry promotion, reviews, recognitions, 2010; Series 5 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    This folder is part of accession 2010.044
  - Productions [1/2], 2011; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Productions [2/2], 2011; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Writings, Productions, and Publicity, 2007-2014; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    Various publicity.
  - Writings, Productions, and Publicity, 2009 May 02; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    Poster of "City Life"
  - Writings, Productions, and Publicity, 2012-2014; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Writings, Productions, and Publicity, 2014; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Marfield Prize publicity.
- Compact discs, 1987-2017; Series 6
  Arranged alphabetically. When the recording contains interviews with two or more artists the CD is filed in the correct alphabetical location based on the first artists listed. There are four sets of alphabetical lists. Set 1 (Boxes 27-28) goes A-Z by guest/poet with "miscellaneous"general broadcast programs at the end. Set 2 (Beginning with Box 64) also goes A-Z by guest/poet with "miscellaneous"general broadcast programs at the end. Set 3 (Beginning with Box 89) goes A-Z by guest/poet. Set 4 (Beginning with Box 90) is alphabetical by poet name or CD title. CDs of "The Poet and the Poem" broadcasts are listed at the end by year of broadcast. When using the finding aid the best way to find all the records for a particular artists is to conduct a find on this page for the artists name.
  This series contains compact disc recordings of interviews and poetry readings primarily from the series "The Poet and the Poem" produced and hosted by Grace Cavalieri and recorded at the Library of Congress. Additional recordings of collaborative work by Grace Cavalieri and composer Vivian Adelberg Rudow, various recordings by poets, and those CD-ROMs that list only the author's name or a single broadcast of a program, are collected at the end of the sequence under "Miscellaneous Recordings."
  - QUIQUE AVILES, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem From the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58.34
  - Frank Bidart, David Gewanter, and Jane Shore, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem From the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 55.10
  - George Bilgere, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem From the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 57.35
  - Fleda Brown, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 29.00
  - Kenneth Carroll, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Convention 2003 Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 27.00
  - Kenneth Carroll, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:57
  - Lucille Clifton, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:54
  - Lucille Clifton, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 29:23
  - Michael Collier, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 57:21
  - Billy Collins, U.S. Poet Laureate, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. 29:38; 2. 27:00 Total Time 56:48
  - Tory Dent, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. 31:53; 2. 25:20 Total Time 57:13
  - Rita Dove #2, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 57:59
  - Cornelius Eady, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 57:05
  - Claudia Emerson, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:13
  - Daniel Mark Epstein, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:58
  - Gary Fincke, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 28:40
  - Nick Flynn, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. 28:34; 2. 30:04 Total time 58:38
  - David Gewanter, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. 29:44; 2. 28:56 Total time 58:40
  - Maria Mazziotti Gillan, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:42
  - Daniela Gioseffi, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 56:01
  - Louis Gluck, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 56:06
  - Louis Gluck U.S. Poet Laureate, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 55:27
  - Patrick Gray, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:43
  - Major Jackson, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Sheila Carter Jones, undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Convention 2003 Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 28:44
  - Katia Kapovich, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 59:00
  - Dolores Kendrick, undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:36
  - Dolores Kendrick, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. PT .1 31:49 2. PT.2 27:13
  - Ted Kooser U.S. Poet Laureate and Pulitzer Prize winner, undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 57:39
  - Ted Kooser U.S. Poet Laureate, undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 57:10
  - Stanley Kunitz, undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. PT.1 30:24 and 2. PT.2 25:44
  - Campbell McGrath, undated (Box 27, Folder 32)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. 31:44 and 2. 27:14 Total time 58:58
  - Heather McHugh, undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 1. 31:25 and 2. 28:02 Total time 59:27
  - Leon Markowitz, undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Convention 2003 Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 28:56
  - Herbert Martin, undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:39
  - Herbert Martin, undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Convention 2003 Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 27:09
  - W.S. Merwin, undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 54:31
  - E. Ethelbert Miller, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the Library of Congress Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 58:59
  - Stephen Myers, undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
    Interview from the Poet and the Poem from the International Society of Poets Grace Cavalieri producer/host. Time of recording 28:34
  - Naomi Shihab Nye, undated (Box 27, Folder 40)